the water.
Then it becomes a very small volume
So I have calculated it to about two liters.
So if you have been out somewhere and freeze for example
So you can take and shower warm water for 15-20 minutes.
It is the same water that you reuse.
Then they soap it in with shampoo and rinse it off after
Has rinsed off it.
Then it empties the amount of water and replenishes two liters of water
Which means you have six liters, 3 two liters.
So on six liters you have as long hot shower as you want.
Just make about six liters of water.
The real ones you've gone another step and that is that you have carbon filters
and UV filter and recycle the same water again
And again and again.
That I have no sink in where I live.
So it must be a bucket instead so that one a little provisional
Moves the stuff back and forth.
But that is a transient problem.
Right size of the table?
Yes, it is generously increased, but it is all right for me.
So time, what is allowed to control.
The bed is important.
It is many hours a day you use so it should be stuck.
I don't mind those who make other solutions,
But for me it is a matter of course that it should be stuck.
The table must be a solid it is a laser cut chipboard
with hidden suspension so it will be very stable
But no table legs.
This table is a central part.
You also have a large screen that can fold forward
So when you sit and work with it you have a generous screen to work with.
But if you sit and jaw dinner and you may have visits
Then the screen just folds into the wall so that it disappears and then you have a visit.
Folds down a sit device out of the wall as well.
What kind of stuff hangs on the wall?
Wall covering becomes 3D cork, a product I found in Poland
So here are internal dimensions that I work with
And that's something I didn't know.
By the way.
You have 250 in the maximum width of trucks
But cooling containers have disputes due to thick insulation
So I do not want to lose the width inside.
Received exemption for 255 so that the width is 255 and internal
is 246, 225 in ceiling height and 620.
That volume is exactly what I need to fit
With what I want with me.
Then I have a big shower toilet but the shower toilet
using a couple of times a day for a few minutes
And then you don't have much benefit from that volume.
So what I did instead is that you have a wardrobe device
which is generously grown.
I will build with slide so you pull out the entire closet
And it works like a door out there.
It has room for the shower and the equivalent we have at the kitchen
have in the refrigerator and in the refrigerator so that the whole modules go out
And there both toilet and shower have available.
The idea is that it is quite close to Sweden.
If I lived in it for two months and discover that deficiencies and errors are corrected
So it is quite easy to find back to Sweden and fix it.
Works everything as it is intended then I just move on
Through Estonia, Latvia, Lithuania and all of Europe.
So May is leaving me from here and so the plan is that I am gone for a couple of years
So we'll see where it lands somewhere.
I have nothing that keeps me here in Sweden.
Either settle in Poland or in Portugal or whatever it will be.
But you band all that you do too.
Yes, I have started a Youtube channel for step one